<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Lagos City</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="home_screen_title">Know My City</string>
    <string name="coffee_shop_title">Coffee Shops</string>
    <string name="location_list_title">Location List</string>
    <string name="restaurants_title">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="kid_friendly_places_title">Kid Friendly Places</string>
    <string name="parks_title">Parks</string>
    <string name="shopping_center_title">Shopping Centers</string>
    <string name="details_title">%d Details</string>
    <string name="top_beans_name">Top Beans Coffee and More</string>
    <string name="top_beans_address">1436 Sanusi Fafuriwa street, Victoria Island, Lagos, 106104 Lagos</string>
    <string name="top_beans_details">Known for its warm atmosphere and extensive menu, including a standout Japanese cheesecake.</string>
    <string name="vestar_coffee_name">Vestar Coffee</string>
    <string name="vestar_coffee_address">26A Oju Olobun Close, Victoria Island</string>
    <string name="vestar_coffee_details">Offers premium quality, small-batch handcrafted coffee in a minimalist modern setting.</string>
    <string name="myYa_cafe_name">MyYa\'s Cafe</string>
    <string name="myYa_cafe_address">Plot 6 Muiz Banire Street, Lekki PhaseII, Lagos 100001, Lagos</string>
    <string name="myYa_cafe_details">A pocket-friendly spot offering a serene environment for work or relaxation with locally sourced smoothies.</string>
    <string name="bubble_tii_name">Bubble Tii (BOBA)</string>
    <string name="bubble_tii_address">Aaron\'s Mail, Olabunmi Owo Street, Lekki PhaseI, Suit 16, Lagos 550104 </string>
    <string name="bubble_tii_details">A fun blend of natural, organic, fresh bubble tea or "boba tea" drinks. Located in the heart of Lekki Phase1. Bubbletii, serves yummy Hong Kong Egg Waffles (Bubble waffles), Fresh filled donuts and apple crumble tarts. All drinks are handcrafted and topped with natural tapioca balls, fruit jellies and or popping boba to finish. The café also serves hot croissant, fresh juices and coffee. With gluten free and vegan options everyone can have an experiential treat.</string>
    <string name="la_pointe_cafe_name">La Pointe Café</string>
    <string name="la_pointe_cafe_address">4A Akin Olugbade Street, off Idowu Martins Street, Victoria Island, Lagos</string>
    <string name="la_pointe_cafe_details">Known for its homely atmosphere and Starbucks coffee, perfect for a quick breakfast date.</string>
    <string name="delis_coffee_name">Delis Coffee</string>
    <string name="delis_coffee_address">1291 Akin Adesola Street, Victoria Island</string>
    <string name="delis_coffee_details">Found at 1291 Akin Adesola Street, Victoria Island, Delis Coffee offers a variety of coffee drinks, gourmet sandwiches, and a relaxing bar-meets-café atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="hans_and_rene_name">Hans &amp; Rene</string>
    <string name="hans_and_rene_address">1A Ozumba Mbadiwe Ave, Victoria Island, Lagos 106104, Lagos</string>
    <string name="hans_and_rene_details">A boutique café and gelateria offering a wide variety of pastries, cakes, and over 40 flavors of gelato and sorbets.Located at 1a Ozumba Mbadiwe Avenue, Victoria Island, this boutique café offers a variety of gelato flavors, freshly baked pastries, and other treats in a stylish setting.</string>
    <string name="art_cafe_name">Art Cafe</string>
    <string name="art_cafe_address">282 Akin Olugbade, off Idowu Martins, Victoria Island, Lagos</string>
    <string name="art_cafe_details">A multi-faceted space that includes a café, art gallery, and dance studio, perfect for enjoying a cup of coffee while appreciating art.</string>
    <string name="pause_cafe_and_espresso_bar_name">Pause Café &amp; Espresso Bar</string>
    <string name="pause_cafe_and_espresso_bar_address">1 Bisway Street, Maroko Lekki 106014, Lagos</string>
    <string name="pause_cafe_and_espresso_bar_details">Ideal for a relaxed outing with its picturesque outdoor setting and diverse menu.</string>
    <string name="caffe_tranche_by_araba_name">Caffe Tranche by Araba</string>
    <string name="caffe_tranche_by_araba_address">148 Olosa street, off Karim Kontu, Lagos</string>
    <string name="caffe_tranche_by_araba_details">This café provides a relaxing oasis with an outdoor space adorned with palm trees, ideal for a relaxing date or Sunday brunch.</string>


    <string name="rufusAndBeeName">Rufus And Bee</string>
    <string name="rufusAndBeeAddress">Okunde Bluewaters scheme Twinwaters Lagos, off Remi Olowude St, Eti-Osa, Lekk</string>
    <string name="rufusAndBeeDetails"> This entertainment center offers a variety of arcade games, bowling, and a Tex-Mex restaurant, making it a fun spot for both kids and adults.</string>
    <string name="omu_resort_name">Omu Resort</string>
    <string name="omu_resort_address">1 Asiwaju Bola Tinubu Wy, Ibeju, Lekki 105101, Lagos</string>
    <string name="omu_resort_details">A popular destination for families, Omu Resort in Ibeju Lekki offers a zoo, amusement park, and water park, set in a lush environment.</string>
    <string name="maxtitvity_name">Maxtivity</string>
    <string name="maxtivity_address">Landmark Beach, 4 Water Corporation Dr, Oniru, Lagos</string>
    <string name="maxtivity_details">This family entertainment center at Circle Mall in Lekki offers a variety of attractions including bumper cars, soft play, arcade games, and climbing walls.</string>
    <string name="funville_name">FunVille</string>
    <string name="funville_address"> Akin Adesola St, Victoria Island, Lagos 101241, Lagos</string>
    <string name="funville_details"> An indoor playground in Victoria Island, Funville is designed for kids aged 3 to 12, with activities and a small diner on site.</string>
    <string name="funtopia_name">Funtopia Leisure Resort</string>
    <string name="funtopia_address">Lekki Estate Phase 1, Ibeju Lekki, Lekki</string>
    <string name="funtopia_details">Funtopia located in Ibeju-Lekki, Lagos is an ideal children’s world. There are fun sections for kids below the age of three; parents can have fun with their children when they play, swim and enjoy several water sports. There are also arcade and computer games in ‘Cusco city’, billiards and table tennis in ‘The Shed’ and a wide variety of other activities to keep your children entertained.</string>
    <string name="whispering_palms">Whispering Palms</string>
    <string name="whispering_palms_address"> Whispering Palms Iworo Road Turn at Aradagun Bus Stop Do NOT branch at Mowo Town, Off Lagos Badagry Express Way, Amuwo Odofin, Badagry 100101, Lagos</string>
    <string name="whispering_palms_details">A resort offering ecological and aquatic tourism along the Lagos Lagoon, Whispering Palms provides a peaceful getaway with activities for both relaxation and fun.</string>
    <string name="lekki_leisure">Lekki Leisure Lake</string>
    <string name="lekki_leisure_address"> CFF6+FVW, Lekki Leisure Lake, Adekunle Animashaun Drive, Marwa, Off Lekki Phase 1, Lekki, Adekunle Animashaun Dr, Eti-Osa, Lagos 106104</string>
    <string name="lekki_leisure_details">This lakeside resort offers various water sports, quad biking, and other outdoor activities, ideal for an adventurous family day out.</string>
    <string name="dream_world">Dream World Africana</string>
    <string name="dream_world_address">First Right Turn After The 2nd Tollgate KM 20 Lekki-Ajah Expressway, Lekki Penninsula II, Lekki</string>
    <string name="dream_world_details">Dreamworld Africana is an amusement and theme park situated in Lekki, Lagos State. Established in 2018, Dreamworld covers an area of 10 acres and re-opened to the public in 2013. The park is one of the main amusement parks in the city. The park provides many attractions to keep its visitors excited.Dreamworld Africana is an amusement park featuring various rides and attractions for children, including carousels, roller coasters, and a play area. It’s a great place for families to spend a fun-filled day.</string>
    <string name="popsicle_name">Popsicle by Happy Hour</string>
    <string name="popsicle_address">8 Olajumoke Obasa Cl, Alaka, Lagos 101241, Lagos</string>
    <string name="popsicle_details">This spot offers a delightful experience for kids with a sweet tooth. Located at Town Square Mall in Magodo, it serves a wide variety of popsicles in different flavors, perfect for a cool treat on a hot day.</string>
    <string name="hakuna_name">Hakuna Matata Theme Park</string>
    <string name="hakuna_address"> Eko Atlantic City, Ahmadu Bello Wy, Victoria Island, Lagos 106104, Lagos</string>
    <string name="hakuna_details">Divided into wet and dry zones, this theme park offers a range of fun activities, including slides, small pools, and playgrounds. It’s an excellent choice for a family day out with young children​</string>


    <string name="shirp_name">Shiro Lagos</string>
    <string name="shiro_address">Block XVI 3 &amp; 4 Victoria Island Oniru Estate, Eti-Osa, Lagos 101241</string>
    <string name="shirodetails"> Known for its Pan-Asian cuisine, Shiro is a popular upscale spot for sushi and other Asian-inspired dish.  Has outdoor seating · Serves great cocktails · Serves vegan dishes</string>
    <string name="cactusName">Cactus Restaurant</string>
    <string name="cactusAddress">20/24 Ozumba Mbadiwe Ave, Victoria Island, Lagos 106104, Lagos</string>
    <string name="cactusDetails">Offers a combination of international cuisine and bakery delights, located on Victoria Island. Has all you can eat · Has outdoor seating · Serves great cocktails</string>
    <string name="z_kitchen_name">Z Kitchen</string>
    <string name="z_kitchen_address">19 Saka Tinubu St, Victoria Island, Lagos 106104, Lagos</string>
    <string name="z_kitchen_details">A stylish restaurant serving international cuisine with a modern touch. Upscale international cuisine &amp; cocktails in a chic setting with a smoking patio &amp; 2 bars. Reservations required · Has all you can eat · Has outdoor seating</string>
</resources>